[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which team won the second Super Bowl?", "correct_answer": "The Green Bay Packers", "incorrect_answers": ["The New York Jets", "The Washington Redskins", "The Kansas City Chiefs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actor did Leonardo DiCaprio befriend in 1990?", "correct_answer": "Tobey Maguire", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Damon", "Ben Afleck", "Matt LeBlanc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A record by what performer was playing right before Anthony got his revenge in the film Dead Presidents?", "correct_answer": "James Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Issac Hayes", "Curtis Mayfield", "Stevie Wonder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clark Gable was in the Army  Air Corps during World War II. Who signed his discharge  papers?", "correct_answer": "Ronald Reagan", "incorrect_answers": ["Hap Arnold", "John Marshall", "George Patton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1995 movie was the lucky winner of a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture.", "correct_answer": "Showgirls", "incorrect_answers": ["Its Pat!", "The Scarlet Letter", "Waterworld"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are Red-eyed Tree Frogs carnivores?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other common name is used for a mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "Waterdog", "incorrect_answers": ["Water Canine", "Mud Dog", "Salamander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Biblical prophet, mentioned in two books of the Bible, was swallowed by a great leviathan?", "correct_answer": "Jonah", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeroboam", "Joshua", "Jeremiah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms means fear of pins and needles?", "correct_answer": "Belonephobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Batrachophobia", "Batophobia", "Barophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to anonymous researches, conducted in the USA in 2002, most teenagers aged 12-17 have at least tried Marijuana.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means a baked dish made mainly of eggs and milk?", "correct_answer": "Quiche", "incorrect_answers": ["Quivive", "Quoin", "Quiddich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you are solving a word problem for 2 unknowns, how many equations will you need?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "4", "1"]}]